Finding Aid of the Society of American Archivists Records, 1935-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1935-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 172; 271.9 cubic ft. (385 boxes, including 16 audio cassettes and 33 videocassettes) 1 oversize folder 7,545 digital files (26.2 GB) 1 film reel 5 microfilm reels approximately 170 books and serial titles
  - 9. Annual Meeting Files, Audio-Visual Formats, and Publications, 200/09
    - 1. Annual Meetings, 1937-2014, 200/09/01; 4 cubic ft. (4 boxes)
      - Boston, MA, 2004
        - Host Committee, 2003-2004 (Electronic \SAA 2004 Host Committee\)
        - Program, 2004 (Folder 38)
      - New Orleans, LA, 2005
        - Program, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Washington, DC, 2006
        - Program, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Chicago, IL, 2007
        - Program, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - San Francisco, CA, 2008
        - Program, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Austin, TX, 2009
        - Program, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Washington, DC, 2010
        - Program, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Chicago, IL, 2011
        - Program, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - 2. Photographs, 1937-2014, 200/09/02; 1.9 cubic ft. (3 box and 1 oversize folder)
      This series contains photographs mainly of SAA officers and Council members taken at annual meetings. The bulk of the annual meeting photographs date from the late 1950s to the mid-1970s.
      - Alldredge, Everett, 1964 (Box 1, Photograph 364)
      - Alldredge, Everett, 1970 (Box 1, Photograph 325)
      - Alldredge, Everett, Vice-President Elect, 1962 (Box 1, Photograph 251)
      - American Archivist, 1982: vol 45, #1, Layout Photographs (Box 1, Photograph 503-504)
      - Angel, Herbert
        - President, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Photograph 107-108)
        - President, undated (Box 1, Photograph 338)
      - Annual Meeting, 1937 (Washington, D.C.)
        - Banquet (Box 1, Photograph 1-4)
        - Banquet (Box 1, Photograph 311)
        - Banquet (Box 1, Photograph 377)
      - Annual Meeting, 1949 (Quebec City, Quebec, Canada). L-R: Brayer, Buck, Lovett, Mrs. Buck, Norton, Chutfield, Lamb (Box 1, Photograph 257)
      - Annual Meeting, 1951 (Annapolis, Maryland): Banquet (Oversize 1, Photograph 522)
      - Annual Meeting, 1953 (Dearborn and Detroit, Michigan)
        - Lovett (on right) (Box 1, Photograph 258)
        - Margaret Norton (Box 1, Photograph 259)
        - Posner, Ernst (light suit) and Father Brown (on right) (Box 1, Photograph 262)
        - Posner, Ernst Waving (Box 1, Photograph 260)
        - Clinton Inn (Box 1, Photograph 261)
      - Annual Meeting, 1956 (Washington, D.C.) (Box 1, Photograph 10)
      - Annual Meeting, 1956 (Washington, D.C.)
        - Banquet (Box 1, Photograph 6)
        - Banquet (Oversize 1, Photograph 7-8)
        - Banquet (Box 1, Photograph 368)
        - Ernst Posner Delivers Presidential Address (Box 1, Photograph 12)
        - Officers and Council: L-R Standing: Brown, Grover, Trever; Sitting: Posner, Overman, Smith, Renze, deValinger, Edmund (Box 1, Photograph 9)
      - Annual Meeting, 1957 (Columbus, Ohio)
        - Committee on State Archives Exhibit, L-R: M. Bryan, D. Renze, W. Jenkins (Oversize 1, Photograph 13)
        - Dolores Renze at Registration Desk (Box 1, Photograph 16)
        - Governor's Reception: L-R Foreground: Renze, deValinger, Bryan, Gov. O'Neill (Box 1, Photograph 14)
        - Officers L-R: deValinger, Holmes, Overman, Cappon, Renze (Box 1, Photograph 18-19)
      - Annual Meeting, 1959 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania) (Box 1, Photograph 263)
      - Annual Meeting, 1959 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
        - Hughes, Charles (Box 1, Photograph 373)
        - Hutchings, Harold (Box 1, Photograph 303)
        - Illinois Delegation, L-R: G. Lennes, M.L. McCree, J. Haring, A. Motley. (Box 1, Photograph 273)
        - L-R: C. Lord, L. Du Page, Unidentified, C. Crittenden, D. Duniway (Box 1, Photograph 376)
        - L-R: C. Lord, R. Nichol, Mayor Delworth, C. Hughes, C. Crittenden (Box 1, Photograph 374)
        - L-R: deValinger, Renze, Silvestro, Lord, Nichol, Delworth, Bryan. Rest Unidentified (Box 1, Photograph 372)
        - Session Photo (Box 1, Photograph 375)
      - Annual Meeting, 1960 (Boston, Massachusetts)
        - Bryan, Mrs. and John Porter, Kresge Hall, Harvard Business School (Box 1, Photograph 266)
        - Kresge Hall, Harvard Business School. L-R: Unidentified, Lovett, Davidson (Box 1, Photograph 265)
        - L-R: Leon deValinger, Wayne Grover, Dolores Renze, Mary Givens Bryan, Philip Hamer (Box 1, Photograph 337)
        - Norton, Miss (Box 1, Photograph 264)
      - Annual Meeting, 1961 (Missouri)
        - Banquet (Oversize 1, Photograph 22)
        - Banquet (Box 1, Photograph 390)
        - Banquet (Oversize 1, Photograph 523)
        - Candid Photographs, Individuals Unidentified (Box 1, Photograph 21)
      - Annual Meeting, 1962 (Rochester, New York) (Box 1, Photograph 250)
      - Annual Meeting, 1962 (Rochester, New York)
        - Address by James Card, Eastman House (Box 1, Photograph 29-31)
        - Address by James Card (Box 1, Photograph 69-70)
        - Address by James Card (Box 1, Photograph 383)
        - Address by Retiring President R. Bahmer (Box 1, Photograph 41-44)
        - Address by Retiring President R. Bahmer (Box 1, Photograph 380)
        - Alldredge, Everett (Box 1, Photograph 67-68)
        - Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 1, Photograph 71)
        - Banquet, Dr. Philip Brooks Presents Leland Prize to Dr. Philip Hamer (Box 1, Photograph 27-28)
        - Baumhofer, Mrs. Hermine, Audio-Visual Records Session Speaker (Box 1, Photograph 384)
        - Head Table, Banquet: L-R: Hamer, deValinger, Lamb, Hamer, Kahn, Kahn, Bahmer, Lamb, Renze (Box 1, Photograph 48-49)
        - Hermine Baumhofer, Chief USAF Motion Picture Film Deposit., Wright-Patterson AFB, Ohio, Address (Box 1, Photograph 58-60)
        - James I. Robertson Address (Box 1, Photograph 53-57)
        - James I. Robertson, Executive Director of the Civil War Centennial Committee (Box 1, Photograph 50-52)
        - L-R: Wm. Alderson, Harold Pinkett, Robert Brown, Al Leisinger, Jr. (Box 1, Photograph 32-34)
        - Officer/Council. L-R: Alldredge, de Valinger, Renze, Jones; Back L-R: Dodson, Suelflow, Lamb, Skordas, Munden (Box 1, Photograph 35-37)
        - Officers. L-R: Dolores Renze, Everett Alldredge, H.G. Jones, Leon de Valinger (Box 1, Photograph 38-40)
        - Opening Luncheon, Address by Beaumont Newhall of Eastman (Box 1, Photograph 26)
        - Opening Luncheon, Address by Beaumont Newhall of Eastman (Box 1, Photograph 61-63)
        - Robert Bahmer Conferring Certificate of Elected Fellow on Al Leisinger, Jr. (Box 1, Photograph 45-47)
      - Annual Meeting, 1963 (Raleigh, North Carolina)
        - AASLH-SAA Meeting: L-R: Katsaras, Bahmer, Alldredge, Hill, Beach, Brooks, Dodson, Jones, Skordas (Box 1, Photograph 117)
        - Baumhofer, Hermine, Fellow (Box 1, Photograph 389)
        - Crittenden, Christopher Receives AASLH Award (Box 1, Photograph 111-113)
        - Dietrich, Mabel, Fellow (Box 1, Photograph 385)
        - Gaus, Robert, Fellow (Box 1, Photograph 388)
        - Jennings, John, Fellow (Box 1, Photograph 387)
        - Mason, Philip, Fellow (Box 1, Photograph 386)
      - Annual Meeting, 1964 (Austin, Texas)
        - By H.G. Jones (Box 1, Photograph 477)
        - Alamo (Box 1, Photograph 199-200)
        - Alamo, L-R: Carrol Hart, Charles Lee, A.K. Johnson (Box 1, Photograph 204)
        - Alderson, William T. Introducing President Alldredge (Box 1, Photograph 181)
        - Alldredge, Everett Presents Fellow Certificate for James Fuch to P. Brooks (Box 1, Photograph 326)
        - Alldredge, Everett Presents Fellow Certificate to August Suelflow (Box 1, Photograph 328)
        - Alldredge, Everett Presents Fellow Certificate to Dorman Winfrey (Box 1, Photograph 327)
        - Alldredge, Everett Presents Fellow Certificate to Dorman Winfrey (Box 1, Photograph 331)
        - Alldredge, Everett Presents Scroll of American State Archives to Ernst Posner (Box 1, Photograph 183-184)
        - Alldredge, Everett Presents Scroll of American State Archives to Ernst Posner (Box 1, Photograph 332)
        - Alldredge, Everett, Presidential Address (Box 1, Photograph 190)
        - Alldredge, Everett, Presidential Address (Box 1, Photograph 215)
        - Banquet (Box 1, Photograph 180)
        - D.K. Taylor, Bruce Harding, Olney Hill (right, rear) (Box 1, Photograph 313)
        - de Valinger, Jr., Leon presents Fellows Certificate for A. Conrad, Alldredge looks on (Box 1, Photograph 334)
        - Distinguished Service Award Presented to North Carolina Department of Arch./Hist. L-R: Jones, Alldredge, Patterson (Box 1, Photograph 182)
        - Evans, Frank B. Awarded Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 189)
        - Evans, Frank Receives Fellows Certificate from Everett Alldredge (Box 1, Photograph 333)
        - Hall of Horns in San Antonio (Box 1, Photograph 205)
        - Harding, Bruce and Dorothy Taylor at Cocktail Party (Box 1, Photograph 194)
        - Holmes, Oliver W. Present Leland Award to Gust Skordas of Maryland (Box 1, Photograph 187)
        - Loften, Paul, Chairman of Local Arrangements, and Wife (Box 1, Photograph 179)
        - L-R: Philip Mason, W. Kaye Lamb, Dolores Renze, H.G. Jones (Box 1, Photograph 312)
        - Munden, Ken and Dorothy Hill Gersack (R) at Cocktail Party (Box 1, Photograph 193)
        - Officers, 1964-65, L-R: P. Mason, W.K. Lamb, D. Renze, H.G. Jones (Box 1, Photograph 191)
        - Officers, 1964-65, L-R: P. Mason, W.K. Lamb, D. Renze, K. Munden, H.G. Jones (Box 1, Photograph 192)
        - Quimby, Grace Awarded Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 188)
        - San Antonio Amphitheater (Box 1, Photograph 202)
        - San Antonio Amphitheater (Box 1, Photograph 208)
        - San Antonio Restaurant (Box 1, Photograph 206)
        - San Antonio Restaurant (Box 1, Photograph 211)
        - San Antonio River (Box 1, Photograph 201)
        - San Antonio River (Box 1, Photograph 207)
        - San Antonio River (Box 1, Photograph 209-210)
        - San Antonio River (Box 1, Photograph 212)
        - San Antonio River (Box 1, Photograph 216)
        - San Jose Mission (Box 1, Photograph 198)
        - San Jose Mission (Box 1, Photograph 203)
        - Suelflow, August Awarded Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 185)
        - Sunken Garden in San Antonio (Box 1, Photograph 195)
        - Sunken Garden in San Antonio (Box 1, Photograph 196)
        - Sunken Garden in San Antonio (Box 1, Photograph 197)
        - Winfrey, Dorman Awarded Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 186)
        - Witte Museum, San Antonio (Box 1, Photograph 213-214)
        - Witte Museum, San Antonio-Dorothy Taylor in (Box 1, Photograph 217)
      - Annual Meeting, 1965 (New York, New York)
        - Ernst Posner Accepting the Leland Award from Lester J. Cappon (Box 1, Photograph 122)
        - Ernst Posner Accepting the Waldo Leland Award from President W. Kaye Lamb (Box 1, Photograph 119)
        - Gust Skordas (R) Accepts Distinguished Service Award for Maryland Hall of Records from L. Cappon (Box 1, Photograph 126)
        - Gust Skordas (L) and Rex Beach (R) of Maryland Hall of Records Accepting Distinguished Service Trophy (Box 1, Photograph 130)
        - Lamb, W. Kaye, Presidential Address (Box 1, Photograph 124-125)
        - Mario Fenyo Accepts Gondos Award from Lester Cappon, chairman of Awards Committee (Box 1, Photograph 118)
        - Meustadter, Dr. Richard, Luncheon Speaker (Box 1, Photograph 123)
        - Meyer Fishbien Accepts Fellow's Certificate from Former President Everett Alldredge (Box 1, Photograph 127)
        - Morris L. Rieger Accepts Fellow's Certificate from Former President Everett Alldredge (Box 1, Photograph 121)
        - Riley, Stephen T., Accepting Fellow's Certificate (Box 1, Photograph 129)
        - Santen, Vernon Accepting Fellow's Certificate (Box 1, Photograph 128)
        - Seymour J. Pomrenze Accepts Fellow's Certificate from Former President Everett Alldredge (Box 1, Photograph 120)
      - Annual Meeting, 1967 (Santa Fe, New Mexico) (Box 1, Photograph 147)
      - Annual Meeting, 1967 (Santa Fe, New Mexico)
        - Angel, Herbert Gives Presidential Address (Box 1, Photograph 218)
        - Angel, Herbert, Delivers Presidential Address (Box 1, Photograph 229)
        - Angel, Herbert, President (Box 1, Photograph 143)
        - Awards Luncheon (Box 1, Photograph 155)
        - Capers, Charlotte (L) and Dolores Renze (Box 1, Photograph 152)
        - Davis, Bill and Dolores Renze (Box 1, Photograph 151)
        - Gersack, Dorothy and Dolores Renze (R) (Box 1, Photograph 154)
        - Guthrie, Chester and Dolores Renze (Box 1, Photograph 153)
        - Halpin, Joe (Box 1, Photograph 148)
        - Lovett, Dorothy with Dorothy Shipton (Box 1, Photograph 521)
        - Mane, Rubio, Archivist of Mexico (Box 1, Photograph 146)
        - Posner, Ernst (Box 1, Photograph 144)
        - Posner, Ernst Acknowledges Festschrift. L-R: D. Renze/C. Shipton (Box 1, Photograph 220)
        - Renze, Dolores (Box 1, Photograph 156)
        - Renze, Dolores Presents Fellowship to Charlotte Capers (Box 1, Photograph 223)
        - Renze, Dolores Presents Fellowship to Chester S. Guthrie (Box 1, Photograph 226)
        - Renze, Dolores Presents Fellowship to Dorothy Hill Gersack (Box 1, Photograph 225)
        - Renze, Dolores Presents Fellowship to Edward N. Campbell (Box 1, Photograph 222)
        - Renze, Dolores Presents Fellowship to Jean Stephenson (Box 1, Photograph 227)
        - Renze, Dolores Presents Fellowship to William Benedon (Box 1, Photograph 221)
        - Renze, Dolores Presents Fellowship to William N. Davis (Box 1, Photograph 224)
        - Speakers Table (Box 1, Photograph 157-159)
        - Stephenson, Jean (L) and Dolores Renze (Box 1, Photograph 150)
        - Awards Banquet, L-R: Cappon, Radoff, Munden, Posner, Angel, Brooks, Posner, Bahmer (Box 1, Photograph 219)
        - Benedon, Bill (Box 1, Photograph 149)
      - Annual Meeting, 1968 (Ottawa, Ontario, Canada)
        - Brooks, Philip C., Truman Library, Giving Report of the Nominations Committee (Box 1, Photograph 170)
        - Gear, James L. Receiving Fellows Certificate (Box 1, Photograph 163)
        - Ham, F. Gerald Receiving Fellows Certificate from Herb Angel (Box 1, Photograph 160)
        - Hart, Miss Carroll Receiving Fellows Certificate from Herb Angel (Box 1, Photograph 165)
        - Johnson, A.J., Treasurer, Giving Report (Box 1, Photograph 169)
        - Jones, H.G. Assuming Presidency (Box 1, Photograph 161)
        - Lagerquist, Philip P. Receiving Fellowship Certificate (Box 1, Photograph 172)
        - Lamb, W. Kaye, Canadian Dominion Archivist Accepting Honorary Membership (Box 1, Photograph 167)
        - Lee, Charles E., South Car. A & H Director, Giving Audit Committee Report (Box 1, Photograph 168)
        - Warner, Robert M. Receiving Fellows Certificate from Herb Angel (Box 1, Photograph 162)
        - Whitehill, Walter M. Receiving Fellows Certificate (Box 1, Photograph 164)
        - Woadden, Bob, Toronto, Reading Resolutions (Box 1, Photograph 171)
        - Lovett, Dorothy with Mrs. Bishop; Mrs. Pease (Box 1, Photograph 519)
      - Annual Meeting, 1969 (Madison, Wisconsin)
        - Bellamy, V. Nelle Reads Nominating Committee Report (Box 1, Photograph 240)
        - Conrad, Agnes Reads Resolutions (Box 1, Photograph 239)
        - Cox, H. Bartholomew Receives Gondos Award (Box 1, Photograph 235)
        - Custer, Arline Receives Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 234)
        - Dowd, Mary Jane Receives Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 242)
        - Finch, C. Herbert Receives Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 231)
        - Johnson, A. K. Receives Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 232)
        - Johnson, A. K., Treasurer, Gives Report (Box 1, Photograph 238)
        - Kahn, H. Makes Announcements. L-R: Erney, Knowles, Scotts, Jones, Hamilton, Pinkett (Box 1, Photograph 243)
        - Kahn, Herman Assumes Presidency (Box 1, Photograph 241)
        - North Carolina delegation leaves Raleigh: L-R: Jones, Scotts, Wagstaff, Patterson, Murray, Coker, Mitchell, Toler, Lennon (Box 1, Photograph 245)
        - Patterson, A. M. Receives Fellowship (Box 1, Photograph 233)
        - Renze, Dolores Receives Distinguished Service Award (Box 1, Photograph 236)
        - Scott, Governor Speaks at Opening Lunch. L-R: Kahn, Erney, Knowles, Scott, Jones, Hamilton, Pinkett (Box 1, Photograph 244)
        - Scott, Robert, Governor of North Carolina Gives Luncheon Address (Box 1, Photograph 230)
        - Ham, F. Gerald, Secretary (Box 1, Photograph 237)
        - Shipton, Clifford, President (Box 1, Photograph 166)
      - Annual Meeting, 1972 (Columbus, Ohio): Moseley, Eva (in dark coat)-Ohio Historical Society (Box 1, Photograph 267)
      - Annual Meeting, 1975 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
        - L-R: James Rhoads, Elizabeth Hamer Kegan, Howard Applegate (Box 1, Photograph 276)
        - Bakken, Douglas (Box 1, Photograph 289)
        - Brown, Arnold, Integrated Records Management and Analysis Session Speaker (Box 1, Photograph 300)
        - Business Archives Perspectives Session (Box 1, Photograph 294-297)
        - Calendar Art, Dupont Hall of Records (Box 1, Photograph 309)
        - Campbell, Ann M. (Box 1, Photograph 274)
        - Coker, Fred (Box 1, Photograph 277)
        - Cushman, Helen, Robert Lovett, and Arthur McCourt (Box 1, Photograph 288)
        - Donofrio, John, Edie Heldin, and Les Hough (Box 1, Photograph 305)
        - Dunn, John F., Integrated Records Management and Analysis Session (Box 1, Photograph 301)
        - Dupont Hall of Records (Box 1, Photograph 307)
        - Eleutherian Mills Historical Library Reading Room (Box 1, Photograph 308)
        - Annual Meeting (Box 1, Photograph 310)
        - Frickleton, Gail (Box 1, Photograph 304)
        - Kegan, Elizabeth H. and Howard Applegate (Box 1, Photograph 278)
        - Kurtz, Wilbur-Business Archives Perspectives Session Speaker (Box 1, Photograph 293)
        - Lee, Charles and Robert Lovett (Box 1, Photograph 306)
        - Lennes, Greg and Linda Edgerly (Box 1, Photograph 302)
        - L-R: Bland Blackford, Douglas Tanner, Ronald Perkins (Box 1, Photograph 283)
        - L-R: Duane Swanson, John Donofrio, Judith Lavin (Box 1, Photograph 284)
        - L-R: Edie Hedlin, James Henn, Mary Ruwell, Greg Lennes (Box 1, Photograph 282)
        - L-R: F. Gerald Ham, Mabel Deutrich, J.Frank Cook, Frank Evans (Box 1, Photograph 280)
        - L-R: Gail Frickleton, Harold Hutchings, Wilbur Kurtz, Ethel Von Gerichen (Box 1, Photograph 286)
        - L-R: Judith Lavin, Woodwerth Bein, D.P. Kenney, Gary Saretzky (Box 1, Photograph 285)
        - L-R: Mary Ruwell, Greg Lennes, Bland Blackford, Douglas Tanner (Box 1, Photograph 290)
        - Potosky, Raymond, Integrated Records Management and Analysis Session Speaker (Box 1, Photograph 299)
        - Saretzky, Gary and Edie Hedlin (Box 1, Photograph 287)
        - Saretzky, Gary-Business Archives Perspectives Session Moderator (Box 1, Photograph 291)
        - Session Photo (Box 1, Photograph 279)
        - Session Photo (Box 1, Photograph 281)
        - Stengel, Geoffrey, Business Archives Perspectives Session Speaker (Box 1, Photograph 292)
        - Williams, Richmond D. (Box 1, Photograph 275)
        - Williams, Richmond, Integrated Records Management and Analysis Session speaker (Box 1, Photograph 298)
      - Annual Meeting, 1976 (Washington, D.C.) (Box 1, Photograph 451)
      - Annual Meeting, 1978 (Austin, Texas): L-R: Wilfred Smith, unidentified, unidentified, David B. Gracy (Box 1, Photograph 463)
      - Annual Meeting, 1980 (Cincinnati, Ohio) (Box 1, Photograph 449)
      - Annual Meeting, 1982 (Boston, Massachusetts): Publications Booth (Box 1, Photograph 505)
      - Annual Meeting, 1983 (Minneapolis and St. Paul, Minnesota): Cook, J. Frank, Presidential Address (Box 1, Photograph 442-443)
      - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Chicago) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Atlanta) (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Annual Meeting, 1989 (St. Louis) (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Annual Meeting, 1990 (Seattle) (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Annual Meeting, 1991 (Philadelphia) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Annual Meeting, 1992 (Montreal) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Annual Meeting, 1993 (New Orleans) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Annual Meeting, 1994 (Indianapolis) (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Washington D.C.) (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Annual Meeting, 1996 (San Diego) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Annual Meeting, 1997 (Chicago) (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Annual Meeting, 1998 (Orlando) (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Annual Meeting, 1999 (Pittsburgh) (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Annual Meeting, 2000 (Denver) (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Annual Meeting, 2002 (Birmingham) (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Annual Meetings, 2004-2014 (Electronic \Series 9.2\)
      - Archival Repository (Unidentified), Interior View, undated (Photograph 400)
      - Archival Work Areas, Illustrations for Processing Areas Paper of Eleanor McKay, 1976 (Box 1, Photograph 473-475)
      - Archive War of Texas Dedication Plaque, 1979: L-R: Smith, Bateman, Winfrey, Gracy. American Archivist, vol. 43, no. 1, p.120 (Box 1, Photograph 498-499)
      - Archives and Manuscripts: Exhibits, 1980, Layout photos. SAA Basic Manual by G. Casterline (Box 1, Photograph 502)
      - Arnold, Gary and Tom Rieder Processing Records at Ohio Historical Society, undated. Business Archives Manual Photo (Box 1, Photograph 393)
      - Automated Records and Technology Task Force, 1980, DC. L-R: Newberger, Livingston, Baird, Lytle, Naugler, Geda, Mullin, Evans, Abernathy (Box 1, Photograph 501)
      - Bahmer, Bob (L) and Ernst Posner with Clifford Shipton (L) and Rubio Mane in Background at Annual Meeting, Santa Fe, 1967 (Box 1, Photograph 145)
      - Bahmer, Bob, undated (Box 1, Photograph 340-341)
      - Bahmer, R. Presents Festschrift, Archives and the Public Interest to E. Posner at Annual SAA Meeting in Santa Fe, 1967 (Box 1, Photograph 228)
      - Bahmer, Robert, 1961 (Box 1, Photograph 381)
      - Bakken, Douglas. 1979 (Box 1, Photograph 423)
      - Bangladesh Archives staff members. From American Archivist, vol. 41, no. 4, p. 472 (Box 1, Photograph 479-480)
      - Basic Workshop-SAA, Cincinnati, 1980 September 28 (Box 1, Photograph 432)
      - Basic Workshop-SAA, Cincinnati, 1980 September 28 (Box 1, Photograph 452)
      - Bent, Thomas Hart: Mural "The Opening of the West," Harry S. Truman Library, Independence, Missouri, undated (Box 1, Photograph 353)
      - Berkeley Meeting, Awards Banquet, 1981 (Box 1, Photograph 450)
      - Brichford, Maynard, January 3, 1979 (Box 1, Photograph 434)
      - Brichford, Maynard, President, 1980 (Box 1, Photograph 454)
      - Brooks, Philip C., undated (Box 1, Photograph 365)
      - Brooks, Phillip, Director of Truman Library, and William D. Aeschbacker, Director of the Eisenhower Library, 1963 (Box 1, Photograph 114)
      - Bryan, Mary; Phil Hamer; Dolores Renze; Leon de Valinger, (L-R), 1960 (Box 1, Photograph 20)
      - Buck, Solon S., undated. Photo of Portrait (Box 1, Photograph 347)
      - Campbell, Ann Morgan, undated (Box 1, Photograph 524-525)
      - Cappon, Lester, 1966 (Box 1, Photograph 366)
      - Chase Manhattan Archives, 1982 (Box 1, Photograph 506)
      - Chemical Museum and Library Floor Plan, 1871, from H. Pinckett's "Early Records of US Dept. of Agriculture," 1962 (Box 1, Photograph 317)
      - Circus World Museum; Parascandola, Lovett, D., Madison, 1969 (Box 1, Photograph 520)
      - Coca Cola Archives and Visitors Center, Atlanta, undated (Box 1, Photograph 392)
      - Colley, Charles C. 1979 (Box 1, Photograph 422)